Guide to the Rice University Faculty Council records, 1919-2006 UA 106
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: 1996-2006, 243943
  - Faculty Council Budget (1/9/01), 244190 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Examinations and Standing (2001-2002), 244189 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Council (2001-2002), 244188 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Council Business Meeting- February 9, 2001, 244187 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Council Business Meeting- March 16, 2001, 244186 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Council Business Meeting- April 20, 2001, 244185 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Council Business Meeting- May 4, 2001, 244184 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Council Business Meeting- August 27, 2001, 244183 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Council Business Meeting- September 11, 2001, 244182 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Council Business Meeting- September 25, 2001, 244181 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Council Business Meeting- October 26, 2001, 244180 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council: Committee on Committees (2001), 244179 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Council Election (September 2001), 244178 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Council: Election (Spring 2001), 244177 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Council Election Spring 2001 (petitions), 244176 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Council Membership (2001-2002), 244175 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Council: Proceedings (2001-2004), 244174 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Council: Report (Undergrad Courses/Labs taught by non-Tenured Faculty and Grads), 244173 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- January 23, 2001, 244172 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- February 27, 2001, 244171 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- November 13, 2001, 244170 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- December 10, 2001, 244169 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- December 11, 2001, 244168 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Faculty ranks/titles/voting (2001-2002), 244167 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Family Leave (2001), 244166 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Governance (2001), 244165 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Governance/Research (2001-2002), 244164 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Lecturers (2001), 244163 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Minutes (2001-2002), 244162 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Policies: Faculty Performance Reviews (2001), 244161 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Policy Committee (2001-2002) (1/2), 244160 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Policy Committee (2001-2002) (2/2), 244159 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Policy Committee: Mid Term Review (2001-2002), 244158 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Professional Masters Degrees (2001-2002), 244157 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Salaries (2001-2002), 244156 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Sexual Harassment Policy (2001), 244155 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - [Undergraduate] Teaching (2001), 244154 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - University Standing Committee on Benefits (2001-2002), 244153 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - University Website (2001), 244152 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Appeals/Grievances (2002-2003), 244151 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Athletics (2002), 244150 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Athletics (2002-2004), 244149 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Athletics "Fiasco" (2002), 244148 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Athletics Inquiry (2002), 244147 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - "A Vision for Rice University"/Correspondence (2002-2005), 244146 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Committees (2002-2003), 244145 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Committees Reports (2002-2004), 244144 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Committees (2002) (1/2), 244143 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Committees (2002) (2/2), 244142 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Committees (2002-2004) (1/2), 244141 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Committees (2002-2004) (2/2), 244140 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - "Conflict of Interest" (2002), 244139 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Curriculum (2002-2005), 244138 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Council (2002-2003), 244137 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Council (2002-2003), 244136 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council (2002-2003) (1/2), 244135 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Council (2002-2003) (2/2), 244134 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Council (2002-2003), 244133 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Council: Academic Calendar (2002-2003), 244132 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Council: Athletics (2002-2003), 244131 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Council: Athletics (2002-2004), 244130 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Council Committees (2002-2003), 244129 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Council: Elections (2002), 244128 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Council: Elections (Spring 2002), 244127 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Council Budget (2002-2003), 244126 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- January 22, 2002, 244125 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- February 12, 2002, 244124 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- February 26, 2002, 244123 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- March 19, 2002, 244122 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- March 26, 2002 (Athletics Issues), 244121 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- April 2, 2002, 244120 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- April 4, 2002, 244119 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- May 7, 2002, 244118 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- August 26, 2002, 244117 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- September 10, 2002, 244116 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- September 24, 2002, 244115 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- October 8, 2002, 244114 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- October 22, 2002, 244113 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- November 12, 2002, 244112 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- December 16, 2002, 244111 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- December 17, 2002, 244110 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Council Report: Affordability Champion of the US (2002), 244109 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Council: Report on Research Faculty (2002), 244108 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Council: University Committees (2002-2003), 244107 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - General Faculty (10/29/2002), 244106 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Grievances (5/02), 244105 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Research Faculty Report (2002), 244104 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Senate Creation/Governance (2002-2006), 244103 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Sorbonne/Rice Degree (2002), 244102 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - University Council (2002), 244101 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Action (2003-2004), 244100 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Admissions (2003), 244099 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Agenda (2003-2004), 244098 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Appeals and Grievances (2003), 244097 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Appeals and Grievances (2003), 244096 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Appeals and Grievances (2003), 244095 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Appeals and Grievances (2003-2004), 244094 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Amendment to Faculty Family, Primary Caregiver, Medical, Professional Leaves (20, 244093 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Athletics at Rice: A Report to the Faculty Council (2003), 244092 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Athletics (2003), 244091 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Athletics (2003), 244090 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Athletics Report/Gillis (2003), 244089 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Commencement (November 18, 2003), 244088 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Committees (mailings) (2003), 244087 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Distribution Requirements (2003), 244086 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Elections (2003-2005), 244085 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Council (2003), 244084 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Council (2003-2004) (1/2), 244083 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Council (2003-2004) (2/2), 244082 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council Board (2003-2004), 244081 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Council Committee Assignments (2003-2004), 244080 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Council Committee on Committees (2003-2004) (1/2), 244079 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Council Committee on Committees (2003-2004) (2/2), 244078 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Council Database (2003-2005), 244077 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Council: Degree Changes/high school students/Athletics (2003), 244076 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Council Elections (2003), 244075 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Council Election (March 2003), 244074 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council Elections Committee (2003), 244073 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Council: Elections (examples) (2003), 244072 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Council: "Election Paradox" (2003), 244071 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Council: General Counsel (2003), 244070 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Council: Governance (2003-2004) (1/2), 244069 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Council: Governance (2003-2004) (2/2), 244068 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Council: Honors Council Issue (2003), 244067 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Council: Intellectual Property Policy (2003), 244066 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Council: Faculty Meeting Minutes (2003), 244065 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- January 14, 2003, 244064 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- February 11, 2003, 244063 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- February 20, 2003 (AD HOC Honors Council and Faculty Council), 244062 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- February 25, 2003, 244061 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- March 4, 2003, 244060 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- March 25, 2003, 244059 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- April 1, 2003, 244058 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- April 8, 2003, 244057 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- April 15, 2003, 244056 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- May 8, 2003, 244055 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- August 25, 2003, 244054 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- September 8, 2003 (Mary McIntire), 244053 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- September 22, 2003, 244052 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- September 29, 2003 (Gillis/Barnett/Levy), 244051 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- October 6, 2003, 244050 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- November 3, 2003, 244049 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- November 19, 2003, 244048 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- December 8, 2003, 244047 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- December 8, 2003, 244046 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Council: Honor Council (2003), 244045 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Council: Honor Council Appeals Board (2003), 244044 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Council: Honors Council Issue (2003), 244043 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Council: Members (2003), 244042 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Council Minutes (9/29/2003), 244041 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Council: Policies (2003), 244040 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Council: Presidential Search (2003), 244039 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Council: Presidential Search Committee (2003), 244038 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council: Professorships in Practice (2003), 244037 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Council: Promotions and Tenures (2003), 244036 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Council: Reporting of Final Grades by Faculty (2003), 244035 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Council Reports to President Gillis (2003), 244034 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Council: Rice News (2003), 244033 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Council: Student Association (2003), 244032 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Council: Thresher (2003), 244031 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Governance Subcommittee (2003), 244030 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Governance Committee (Caldwell Materials) (2003-2004), 244029 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Governance (2003-2004), 244028 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Governance- Amherst College (2003), 244027 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Governance- Barnard College (2003), 244026 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Governance- Brown University (2003), 244025 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Governance- Brown University (2003), 244024 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Governance- Bryn Mawr College (2003), 244023 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Governance- Carleton College (2003), 244022 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Governance- Columbia University (2003), 244021 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Governance Committee: Gerber/Rabbin (2003), 244020 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Governance- Cornell University (2003), 244019 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Governance- Dartmouth College (2003), 244018 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Governance- Duke University (2003) (1/2), 244017 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Governance- Duke University (2003) (2/2), 244016 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Governance- Emory University (2003), 244015 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Governance/Faculty Handbook Research/Miscellaneous (2003), 244014 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Governance- Georgetown University (2003), 244013 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Governance- Harvard University (2003), 244012 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Governance- Johns Hopkins University (2003), 244011 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Governance- Massachusetts Institute of Technology (2003), 244010 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Governance- Mount Holyoke College (2003), 244009 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Governance- Northwestern University (2003), 244008 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Governance- Oberlin College (2003), 244007 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Governance- Princeton University (2003), 244006 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Governance- Smith College (2003), 244005 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Governance- Stanford University (2003) (1/2), 244004 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Governance- Stanford University (2003) (2/2), 244003 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Governance- Swarthmore College (2003) (1/2), 244002 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Governance- Swarthmore College (2003) (2/2), 244001 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Governance- Trinity College (2003), 244000 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Governance- Tulane University (2003), 243999 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Governance- University of Chicago (2003), 243998 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Governance- University of Pennsylvania (2003) (1/2), 243997 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Governance- University of Pennsylvania (2003) (2/2), 243996 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Governance- University of Rochester (2003), 243995 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Governance- Vanderbilt University (2003), 243994 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Governance- Washington University in St. Louis (2003), 243993 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Governance- Wellesley College (2003), 243992 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Governance- Wesleyan University (2003), 243991 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Governance- Williams College (2003), 243990 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Governance- Yale University (2003) (1/2), 243989 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Governance- Yale University (2003) (2/2), 243988 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Honor Council (2003-2004), 243987 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Intellectual Property Policy (2003-2004), 243986 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous (2003-2005), 243985 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - New Degree Announcement (2003), 243984 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Presidents Search Committee (2003), 243983 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Professional Titles (2003), 243982 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Reforming the Appeals Process of the Rice University Honor System (2003), 243981 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - University Governance: A Comparative Perspective (2003), 243980 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Athletics (2004), 243979 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Athletics Subcommittee (2004), 243978 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Evaluation of Faculty Poll on Athletics (2004), 243977 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Council Agenda (September 21, 2004), 243976 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Council Agendas (2004), 243975 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Council Agenda (February 19, 2004), 243974 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Council Agenda (November 2004)>, 243973 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Council Business Meeting- April 14, 2004, 243972 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council Calendar (2004-2006), 243971 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Council Committee on Committees Documents (2004), 243970 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Council: Elections (2004), 243969 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Council: Elections (Spring 2004), 243968 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Council Elections Committee- April 7, 2004, 243967 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Council: Leebron and Levy Meetings (2004-2005), 243966 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Council Meetings (March-April 2004), 243965 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- February 10, 2004, 243964 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- January 13, 2004, 243963 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Council Miscellaneous/Correspondence (2004-2005), 243962 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Council Miscellaneous Correspondence (2004), 243961 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Council Poll on the Rice Athletic Program (2004), 243960 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Council Proceedings (2004-2005), 243959 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Council Survey: Women in the Workplace (2004), 243958 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Meetings (2004), 243957 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Governance (2004-2005) (1/2), 243956 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Governance (2004-2005) (2/2), 243955 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Membership of Faculty Council and University Council (2004-2005), 243954 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous/Correspondence (2004), 243953 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Standing Committees (2004-2005), 243952 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Standing Committees (2004-2005), 243951 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Summary of Accomplishments (2004-2005), 243950 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Elections (2005), 243949 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Committees (2005-2006), 243948 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Committees (2005), 243947 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Committees Responses (2005-2006), 243946 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Senate Meeting Details and Agenda (2005), 243945 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Policy Committee (2005), 243944 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Series IV: Documents captured from floppy disks
  - Discs (Box 51)
  - 96-97 FC Merge labels FC Folder, 1998-01-15 (Box 51)
  - FC DataBase Docs Filemaker Pro Doc of 10/98 Updated, 1999-01-14 (Box 51)
  - From: Patten, 1999 (Box 51)
  - Faculty Council Documents 1-14-99 Back-up additions, 1999-12 (Box 51)
  - FC Back Up - Old Prior to '98, 1995-1999 (Box 51)
  - IBM Format for Fac Council 10-2-95 (Box 51)
  - Fac. Council Bylaws - Nov. 1995 Hightower (Box 51)
  - FC Bylaws correct here + on hard disc, 1999-01-14 (Box 51)
  - Standing Committees 89-90 thru 95-96, 1995-1996 (Box 51)
  - Standing Committees 87-93, 1996 (Box 51)
  - Faculty Council Proceedings through 1998, 1995-1998 (Box 51)
  - FC: Various (Part I) *IMPT*, 2001-2003 (Box 51)
  - (FC) Elections (Part 2) *IMPT* (Back-Up), 2002-2003 (Box 51)
  - (FC:) (Pre-Gillis) Old Presidential Search (files) *IMPT*, 2003 (Box 51)
  - FC: Various *IMPT* (Elections/Labels/Etc.) (Pres Search), 2003 (Box 51)
  - 1995, 1993-1995 (Box 51)